Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2 5583/2
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: What does the Actuarial Profession offer you as a career, Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: What will you be doing seven years from now?, Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: If you have an interest in mathematics, Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Newsletter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: New Jersey Public Employer-Employee Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: New Jersey Public Employer-Employee Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: New Jersey Public Employer-Employee Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: New Jersey Public Employer-Employee Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: New Jersey Public Employer-Employee Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The INA Employee Relations Poster Program, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    November 19-20. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Constitution, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: "What It Means To You", Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
    By Edward H. O'Connor. May 28. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Syllabus, Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
    April 2-May 31. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Annual Report Interchemical Corporation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Interchemical Corporation Annual Report, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Interchemical Corporation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Interchemical Corporation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Join InterchemicalA Leader In The Fast Growing Chemical Coatings Industry, Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: A Technical Career with Interchemical, Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: an eye to the public interest, Publication (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Inter-City Motor Carriers Association Inc., Publication (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Interlake Reporter, Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
    December-January. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Your Plan of Group Insurance as an Employee of Intermountain Transportation Company, Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Prison Labor Competition vs. Free Industry, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The IAIABC Handbook, Publication (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: IAIABC Journal, Publication (Box 26, Folder 16)
    Winter. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Development of Workmen's Compensation in the U.S. and Canada, Publication (Box 26, Folder 16)
    By Marshall Dawson. October 4. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Personnel A Challenging Career in Management, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Study of Job Opportunities for Women College Graduates, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Personnel Records, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
    October 20. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: IBM, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: IBM Business Machines, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
    November 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Ideas for Improvenment? Use the Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Poughkeepsie News, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
    December 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Think, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: IBM Business Machines, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: IBM Business Machines, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: The Ultimate In Precision!, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
    March 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: IBM Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: IBM News, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 11: Ideas for Improvement, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 12: Speak Up!, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 13: IBM News, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 14: IBM News, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
    May 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: IBM News, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
    February 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: International Business Machine, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 17: IBM Suggestion Form, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 18: Tool Or Tombstone, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
    By Andrew W. Nelson. May/June. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Fact Book on IBM Speak UP! Program, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 20: Closing The Informatio Gap With More Effective Upward Communications, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
    By Richard M. Wight. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: IBM News, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 22: Lexington Speak Up! Program Revisited, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 23: Speak Up!!!!!!!!, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 24: IBM News, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 25: IBM News, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
    January 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Think, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 27: IBM Annual Report, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: a brief introduction to IBM, Publication (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: facts about positions in IBM for college and universty students, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: About Your Company IBM, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: IBM Room for Achievement, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: a career for you in IBM, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Reflections of your future in IBM, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: My Fair Ladies, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: IBM Careers, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Careers for Technicians at IBM, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Analytically Minded?, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: Leader's Guide -Orientation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 11: IBM, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 12: Reflections of your future in IBM, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 13: Customer Engineering Opportunity for a lifetime career, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 14: IBM Careers, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 15: Company Information Sheet for: International Business Machines Corporation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 16: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 17: IBM Employee Personnel Folder, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 18: The Sheltered Workshop, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 19: Forms, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 20: Personnel Record Forms, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 21: Application For Employment, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
    October 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 23: IBM Employees Health Association Constitution, By-Laws Rules, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 24: Science and Engineering, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 25: IBM Plans for Progress, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
    February 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Advanced Education Opportunities for IBM Engineers and Scientists, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 27: Analytically Minded?, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 28: IBM Engineering Opportunitites, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 29: Room..to grow, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 30: At Work to Prevent Blindness, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 31: IBM, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 32: Consider your future as an IBM Customer Engineer, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 33: IBM Development Engineer, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 34: IBM Research Staff Member, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 35: IBM Data Processing Representative, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 36: IBM Systems Analyst, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 37: IBM Computer Programming, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 38: IBM Business Administration, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 39: IBM System Service Representative, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 40: IBM Manufacturing Research Engineer, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: IBM Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: It Pays To Think, Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: IBM Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: IBM Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Opportunities in IBM, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Board of Directors, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: Agreement For IBM Machine Service, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: About the Company, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: Opportunities Unlimited, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: Unlimited, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: Manufacturing Engineering In IBM, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 8: IBM Engineering Library, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: International Business Machines Corporation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: Papers Presented By Members Of The IBM Engineering Laboratories, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 11: Circulation Control For Libraries, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 12: Introductory Resume for International Business Machines Corporation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: IBM Employees 1966 Stock Purchase Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    April 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: About Your Company IBM, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    December 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: International Business Machines Corporation Health And Accident Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Matching Grants to Education Program of the International Business Machines Corporation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: Generaal Education Program, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: IBM Employee Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: Announcement, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    May 28-June 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Postcards, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 9: IBM Family Hospitalization Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: The Homestead and Park Area, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 11: Group Enrollment, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 12: Watson Trophy Dinner, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 13: Job Assignments For Physically Handicapped Employees, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 14: IBM Country Club, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    July 16. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Publications, Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: 65 annual report, Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: 1964 Annual Report, Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Biennial Report, Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Biennial Report, Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Annual Report, Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: Publications, Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: New Delhi Congress, Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: aims program organization, Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: What does the ICC do for the businessman?, Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: By-Laws, Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Aims Program Organization, Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: Report to Members, Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
    February 6-13. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Annual Report, Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Asian Trade Union College, Publication (Box 26, Folder 27)
    November 30. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Paper of Fouth International Conference, Publication (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Employment In The ICA Foreign Service information for candidates, Publication (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: "the next wenty years in industry", Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Source Material Directory, Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: directory of services and materials, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Directory of Services and Materials, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: contact, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: Ideas from ICIE, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
    April 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Ideas from ICIE, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 6: Dear ICIE Members:, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 7: Revisions In Constitution, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 8: Revisions In Constitution, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 9: Economic Seminars, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 10: Off To Good Star., Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 11: Off To Good Start., Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 12: "Reporting" Stimulates Program, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 13: 1959-1960 President's Report, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 14: Freedoms Foundation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 15: Freedoms Foundation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 16: "Reporting" Stimulates Program., Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 17: Economic Seminars, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 18: Economic Seminars, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 19: Conference Bound, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 20: Conference Bound, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 21: These Are Nominated, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 22: These Are Nominated, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 23: Kennedy-Ives Bill, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 24: Kennedy-Ives Bill, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 25: Conference Is Stimulating, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 26: Conference Is Stimulating, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 27: We're Moving, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 28: Working People In the Next Twenty Years, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
    By Arthur Larson. June 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Industrial Communications of Tomorrow, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
    By Hugh Hoffman. June 18-21. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: "Physical Aspects of Industry In The Next 20 Years", Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
    By Charles Luckman. June 18-21. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Reasons For Needed Constitution Changes, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 32: reporting, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
    June 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Out Of This World, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 34: Out Of This World., Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 35: New Service Planned, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 36: New Service Planned, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 37: Awards Deadline Extended, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 38: Economic Seminars, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 39: Here Are Facts, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 40: Executive Board Meets, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 41: Proceedings of the Seventh Annual Convention of the International Council of Industrial Editors, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
    May 5-7. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Second Intdernational Survey of Company Publications, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: Directory of Services Available to Industrial Editors, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: International council of industrial editors, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    February 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Program 12th Anniversary Conference, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    May 19-22. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: International Council of Industrial Editors Handbook, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Item 6: Handbook, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Item 7: Communication And Competition, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    By John S. Bugas. May 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Address Given at the Annual Conference of the International Council of Industrial Editors, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    By H.J. Cook. May 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: International Council of Industrial Editors, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Box: 27, folder: 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Check List On Organization And Management, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The International Economic Association 1950-1962, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    By Austin Robinson. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Sixth Annual Report 1961-1962, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    September 18. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: General Policies, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Handbook For Employes Of International Harvester Company, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Safety Handbook For Service Parts Operations Personnel, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Labeling for Employee Safety, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Rules of the central safety committee, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: The Foreman and Safety, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Safety Handbook For Sales-Operations Personnel, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Benefit plans for managerial employes, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: these are you International Harvester Company plans that provide life insurance, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: these are your International Harvester Company plans that provide benefits for illness and injury, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: these are your International Harvester Company plans that provide retirement income, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: group term life insurance plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: disability benefits plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: group paid-up life insurance plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: group hospital, surgiacal, and medical expense plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Harvester, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Farm Equipment Research And Engineering Center Employe Handbook, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: International Harvester Company Supervisor's Manual Approved Company Policies, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    August 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: General Office, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: International Harvester Company And Its Employes, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    By J.D. Hackett. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: your future in our future, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Appendix, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Salary Administration, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Barnes Single Spindle Drill Press, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Time Study Observation Sheet, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Waste Reduction Part 1 - General Problems and Departmental Planning, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Waste Reduction Part II - Problems of Specialized Areas, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Industrial Relations and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: History and Development of International Harvester, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Controlled Maintenance, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Visual Aids, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Company Policy, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: The Man and His Job AN Approach to Human Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Harverster School, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Opportunities For Apprenticeship, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Waste Reduction, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
    October 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Effective Speaking, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Visual Aids, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Cooperative Engineering Course, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Job Training Instructor's Guide Unit 388, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: These Are The Harvester Divisions, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
    December 1. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Waste Reduction, Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Operating A Fork Truck, Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Machinery Manufacturing Cost Accounting, Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Departmental Personnel Procedures, Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Facts About Your Course, Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Education and Training at International Harvester, Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
    By Charles L. Walker, Jr. September. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: History and Development of International Harvester 1831-1946, Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Adult Education In Industry, Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: After Graduation Your Opportunity with Harvester, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: When You Choose, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Motor Truck Division Sales, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Farm Equipment Division Sales, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
    September 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Opportunities For Apprenticeship at IH, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: You And IH, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: The Man and His Job An Approach To Human Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: The Man and His Job AN Approach To Human Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Career Opportunities after graduation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Wage Payment Policies, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Your Harvester Pay, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Rules And Regulations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)